
<AutonomousPanel
    controllerClass="MouseModeController">

  <BorderPanel>
	<Center>
	  <FlowPanel xspace="4" yspace="4">
		<ToggleButton title="Pan" group="mouse"
			          value="pan" image="pan" initial="true" action="setPan">
		  <tip>Move the canvas under the viewport</tip>
		  <info>Info about panning</info>
		</ToggleButton>

		<ToggleButton title="Zoom in" group="mouse"
			          value="zoomIn" image="zoom_in" action="setZoomIn">
		  <tip>zoom in by clicking in the image</tip>
		  <info>about the zoom...</info>
		</ToggleButton>

		<ToggleButton title="Zoom out" group="mouse"
			          value="zoomOut" image="zoom_out" action="setZoomOut">
		  <tip>zoom out...</tip>
		</ToggleButton>
		
		<ToggleButton title="Box select" group="mouse"
			          value="box" image="box" action="setBox">
		  <tip>rubber band cursor to select the view area</tip>
		  <info>About the box select mode...</info>
		</ToggleButton>

		<ToggleButton title="Combined mode" group="mouse"
			          value="all" image="all" action="setMulti">
		  <tip>All the actions accesible using differnt mouse buttons</tip>
		  <info>
			The effect of clicking or dragging is determined by
			which mouse button is used and how the mouse is moved.
			-p- To zoom in, click with the left button.
			-p- To zoom out, click with the right button.
			-p- To pan, press and drag with the right button.
			-p- For a box cursor, press the left button at one desired
			corner, drag up and to the left a little way, then drag
			back past the starting point. The cursor will appeaar as you
			recross the starting point.
		  </info>
		</ToggleButton>



		<Checkbox title="Smoothing" label="smooth" id="antialias" action="setAntialias">
		  <tip>turn antialiasing on or off</tip>
		  <info>When this is not selected, lines and borders are drawn
		  by filling in complete pixels only. So, for a black line on a
		  white background all pixels are either black or white.
		  -p- With smoothing ("antialiasing") on, where the line
		  half crosses a pixel the pixel will be filled in a shade of
		  gray. This makes lines and edges look smoother.
		  -p- But it taks the system longer to calculate the shaded
		  pixels and can make the image slow to update.
		  It is most responsive with smoothing switched off.
		  </info>
		</Checkbox>



		<Checkbox title="Labels" label="labels" id="labels" initial="true" action="setLabels">
		  <tip>turn labels on or off on the diagram</tip>
		  <info>
			Labels are handy if you don't know what things are,
			but can get in the way at other times.
		  </info>
		</Checkbox>


	  </FlowPanel>
	</Center>

	<East>
	  <RightFlowPanel xspace="4" yspace="4">
		<Button action="reframe" image="frame.gif">
		  <title>Reframe</title>
		  <tip>reset the ranges so all the data is visible</tip>
		  <info>
			Resets the ranges of the display so that all the data
			is visible.
		  </info>
		</Button>



	  </RightFlowPanel>
	</East>
  </BorderPanel>



</AutonomousPanel>




